The Pachyderm UP018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Pachyderm
1977 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Dean of Student Affairs
UP018
25 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains The Pachyderm student handbook, outlining the rules and regulations of the University. First published in 1977, it replaced the "Student Handbook" and is a successor to the "Ivy Book."
Related Materials
UP016, Ivy Society publications, DCA.
UP022, Tufts College Graduate, DCA
- The Pachyderm, 1977 -- 2009; 1977 -- 2001; UP018.001; 25 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains The Pachyderm, the Tufts student handbook, outlining the rules and regulations of the University. First published in 1977 it replaced the "Student Handbook" and is a successor to the "Ivy Book." Continues from the Ivy Book (1902-71), and the Student Handbook (1972-77).
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Pachyderm, 1977 -- 1978; UP018.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Pachyderm, 1978 -- 1979; UP018.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Pachyderm, 1979 -- 1980; UP018.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Pachyderm, 1980 -- 1981; UP018.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Pachyderm, 1981 -- 1982; UP018.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
  - The Pachyderm, 1983 -- 1984; UP018.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Pachyderm, 1984 -- 1985; UP018.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Pachyderm, 1985 -- 1986; UP018.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - The Pachyderm, 1986 -- 1987; UP018.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9)
  - The Pachyderm, 1987 -- 1988; UP018.001.010.00001 (Box Volume 10)
  - The Pachyderm, 1988 -- 1989; UP018.001.011.00001 (Box Volume 11)
  - The Pachyderm, 1989 -- 1990; UP018.001.012.00001 (Box Volume 12)
  - The Pachyderm, 1990 -- 1991; UP018.001.013.00001 (Box Volume 13)
  - The Pachyderm, 1991 -- 1993; UP018.001.014.00001 (Box Volume 14)
  - The Pachyderm, 1993 -- 1994; UP018.001.015.00001 (Box Volume 15)
  - The Pachyderm, 1994 -- 1995; UP018.001.016.00001 (Box Volume 16)
  - The Pachyderm, 1995 -- 1996; UP018.001.017.00001 (Box Volume 17)
  - The Pachyderm, 1996 -- 1997; UP018.001.018.00001 (Box Volume 18)
  - The Pachyderm, 1997 -- 1998; UP018.001.019.00001 (Box Volume 19)
  - The Pachyderm, 1998 -- 1999; UP018.001.020.00001 (Box Volume 20)
  - The Pachyderm, 2000; UP018.001.021.00001 (Box Volume 21)
  - The Pachyderm, 2000 -- 2001; UP018.001.022.00001 (Box Volume 22)
  - The Pachyderm, 2006 -- 2007; UP018.001.023.00001 (Box Volume 23)
  - The Pachyderm, 2007 -- 2008; UP018.001.024.00001 (Box Volume 24)
  - The Pachyderm, 2008 -- 2009; UP018.001.025.00001 (Box Volume 25)